odili.net 2000-08-19

# Nigeriaworld: Privacy

One of the biggest issues facing the internet today is the protection of the privacy of consumers. Odili.NET has always been a strong proponent of providing accurate and useful information to consumers for free and anonymously. Our privacy policy is outlined below. 

  * The vast majority of services quoted on Odili.NET are provided anonymously. This means... 
    * We will not ask you to provide your name, email address, credit card information, social security number, or phone number.
    * You will be allowed to freely browse Odili.NET for the information you need without providing any information.
    * You will never be asked to "register" in order to access any Odili.NET service.
  * A small number of services quoted on Odili.NET will require a direct response from individual vendors. Such services will be clearly identified and, in such cases, you will be asked to provide contact information for the vendors to contact you. If you utilize this feature, we will only forward this information to the vendors you have selected. Your contact information will promptly be deleted from our servers, and never sold or otherwise used for any purpose.
  * It is Odili.NET's policy to provide contact phone numbers and links out to our participating vendors. You may follow these links or click on an advertiser's banner, but please be advised that Odili.NET does not dictate the Privacy Policy of these vendors' sites.
  * Odili.NET's servers produce industry standard server logs which track which pages are visited, which links are followed, and the IP addresses (not email addresses) of each user. This information is regularly collated for the purpose of monitoring the popularity of various parts of our site. IP addresses are used to distinguish users from each other (ie - how many unique users visited a certain page on a certain day) but are never used to track specific users. All server log information is destroyed once the data collation report is completed. IP addresses are never maintained for more than 30 days.
  * Odili.NET does not use "cookies".
  * If you contact us by email, phone, or US mail, we will only use your personal contact information to reply to your specific request. We will not collect personal information for constructing mailing lists or for resale.
  * This privacy policy shall not apply to individual vendor sites which may have been designed and/or hosted by Odili.NET.

NigeriaWorld works with third parties that serves ads to this site. They include: 

  * Flycast
  * Busrtmedia
  * Advertising.com (Formerly Teknosurf)
  * ValueClick
  * BannerBrokers

> To find out more about how **_Flycast_** manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html>
> 
> To find out more about how **_Burstmedia_** manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.burstmedia.com/release/privacy.asp>
> 
> To find out more about how **_Advertising.com_** manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.advertising.com/privacy/>
> 
> To find out more about how **_ValueClick_** manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://valueclick.com/privacy.html>
> 
> To find out more about how **_BannerBrokers_** manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.bannerbrokers.com/company_info/inf_privacy.html>
One of the biggest issues facing the internet today is the protection of the privacy of consumers. Odili.NET has always been a strong proponent of providing accurate and useful information to consumers for free and anonymously. Our privacy policy is outlined below. 

  * The vast majority of services quoted on Odili.NET are provided anonymously. This means... 
    * We will not ask you to provide your name, email address, credit card information, social security number, or phone number.
    * You will be allowed to freely browse Odili.NET for the information you need without providing any information.
    * You will never be asked to "register" in order to access any Odili.NET service.
  * A small number of services quoted on Odili.NET will require a direct response from individual vendors. Such services will be clearly identified and, in such cases, you will be asked to provide contact information for the vendors to contact you. If you utilize this feature, we will only forward this information to the vendors you have selected. Your contact information will promptly be deleted from our servers, and never sold or otherwise used for any purpose.
  * It is Odili.NET's policy to provide contact phone numbers and links out to our participating vendors. You may follow these links or click on an advertiser's banner, but please be advised that Odili.NET does not dictate the Privacy Policy of these vendors' sites.
  * Odili.NET's servers produce industry standard server logs which track which pages are visited, which links are followed, and the IP addresses (not email addresses) of each user. This information is regularly collated for the purpose of monitoring the popularity of various parts of our site. IP addresses are used to distinguish users from each other (ie - how many unique users visited a certain page on a certain day) but are never used to track specific users. All server log information is destroyed once the data collation report is completed. IP addresses are never maintained for more than 30 days.
  * Odili.NET does not use "cookies".
  * If you contact us by email, phone, or US mail, we will only use your personal contact information to reply to your specific request. We will not collect personal information for constructing mailing lists or for resale.
  * This privacy policy shall not apply to individual vendor sites which may have been designed and/or hosted by Odili.NET.

NigeriaWorld works with third parties that serves ads to this site. They include: 

  * Flycast
  * Busrtmedia
  * ValueClick
  * BannerBrokers

> To find out more about how **_Flycast_** manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.flycast.com/about_us/about-privacy.html>
> 
> To find out more about how **_Burstmedia_** manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.burstmedia.com/release/privacy.asp>
> 
> To find out more about how **_ValueClick_** manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://valueclick.com/privacy.html>
> 
> To find out more about how **_BannerBrokers_** manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to <http://www.bannerbrokers.com/company_info/inf_privacy.html>
